{
    "members": [
        {
            "id": "1",
            "name": "Arman Roshannai",
            "percentage": "13.72",
            "trait_1": {
                "answer": "Farsi",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "2.60",
                "question": "Languages"
            },
            "trait_2": {
                "answer": "Hockey",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "4.40",
                "question": "Sport"
            },
            "trait_3": {
                "answer": "Very important to me",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "3.00",
                "question": "Nurturance"
            },
            "trait_4": {
                "answer": "College Department",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "3.51",
                "question": "Factors of Importance"
            },
            "trait_5": {
                "answer": "Information & Computer Sciences",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "4.29",
                "question": "College Department"
            },
            "type": "Romantic"
        },
        {
            "id": "2",
            "name": "keyan kazemian",
            "percentage": "4.05",
            "trait_1": {
                "answer": "Farsi",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "2.60",
                "question": "Languages"
            },
            "trait_2": {
                "answer": "Information & Computer Sciences",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "4.29",
                "question": "College Department"
            },
            "trait_3": {
                "answer": "University of California, Irvine",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "4.45",
                "question": "University"
            },
            "trait_4": {
                "answer": "Photography",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "7.25",
                "question": "Favorite Hobby"
            },
            "trait_5": {
                "answer": 1,
                "is_scale": true,
                "max_val": 7,
                "percentage": "9.18",
                "question": "Humans are born with an innate purpose"
            },
            "type": "Idealist"
        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "name": "Danial Hashemi",
            "percentage": "13.72",
            "trait_1": {
                "answer": "Iran, Islamic Republic of...",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "0.16",
                "question": "Country"
            },
            "trait_2": {
                "answer": "Very important to me",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "2.44",
                "question": "Risks"
            },
            "trait_3": {
                "answer": "Farsi",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "2.60",
                "question": "Languages"
            },
            "trait_4": {
                "answer": 5,
                "is_scale": true,
                "max_val": 7,
                "percentage": "2.93",
                "question": "Assisting in death"
            },
            "trait_5": {
                "answer": "Not important to me",
                "is_scale": false,
                "max_val": 0,
                "percentage": "3.00",
                "question": "Wealth"
            },
            "type": "Stoic"
        }

    ]


}